// questions.ts
export const questions = [
  {
    question: "When and where is the conference taking place?",
    answer:
      "The 36th Ugnay Palay National Rice R4D Conference will be held on 25-27 November 2025. In-person participants will be gathered at the DA-Crop Biotechnology Center Plenary Hall, DA-PhilRice in Nueva Ecija.",
  },
  {
    question: "Who should attend the conference?",
    answer:
      "The DA-PhilRice hosts the annual Ugnay Palay National Rice Research for Development (R4D) Conference to unite stakeholders – researchers, development workers, scientists, policymakers, government officials, farmers, youth in agriculture, and industry partners – toward transforming the industry.",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the organizer of Ugnay Palay?",
    answer:
      "Ugnay Palay is organized by the Department of Agriculture – Philippine Rice Research Institute.",
  },
  {
    question: "Who can register for the conference?",
    answer:
      "Anyone can register to the 36th Ugnay Palay. We are inviting the rice science community and its stakeholders to attend the Conference. Registration is open until mid-November 2024.",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I register for the conference?",
    answer:
      "You can register for the Ugnay Palay online, either as participant or paper/poster presenter, via",
    link:"https://ugnaypalay.philrice.gov.ph:441/csd/36th/registration-form/ABCDefgHI",
  },
  {
    question: "How will I know if my registration is successful?",
    answer:
      "A notification email will be sent to you once you are done with the registration. If you do not receive your email confirmation within 24 hours, please check your email spam folder and then contact us at ricesecretariat@gmail.com",
  },
  {
    question: "How much does it cost to register for the conference?",
    answer:
      "Attendance to the 36th Ugnay Palay is free of charge. All participants must register and will please arrange and pay for their own accommodation. Nearby accommodation options can be found here",
    link:"https://drive.google.com/file/d/1E_PrvbQpzwDj3ti7RNxiaD6Cg8GcN7wa/view?usp=sharing  ",
  },
  {
    question: "When is the deadline for registration?",
    answer:
      "Participant registration will be open until the second week of November 2025.",
  },
  {
    question: "Can I present at the conference?",
    answer: "Yes. Call for paper and poster",
    link: "https://drive.google.com/file/d/19hkpNdQzX_fxE7XoVe4P3y9BfVsPwdPw/view?usp=sharing",
  },
  {
    question: "Is there a dress code for the conference?",
    answer:
      "The conference attire is business casual for all participants. We recommend dressing comfortably yet professionally for all conference sessions and networking events. Function rooms can get chilly, so we recommend layers for your comfort.",
  },
  {
    question: "How are the conference sessions formatted?",
    answer:
      "There will be three plenary sessions, three panel discussions, and five concurrent sessions.",
  },
  {
    question: "Will conference materials be available?",
    answer:
      "Yes. A souvenir program and copies of the presentation will be available at the Ugnay Palay website and app.",
  },
  {
    question: "Will certificates be given to all participants?",
    answer:
      "Yes. The organizing committee will send out digital certificates of participation through your registered email address within a week after the conference to those who will accomplish the feedback survey questionnaire.",
  },
  {
    question: "Are there Continuing Professional Development (CPD) credit units?",
    answer:
      "Yes. Licensed agriculturists can use their certificates of participation under self-directed learning activities as per accreditation outlined in Section 2 of Resolution No. 1197, Series of 2019, issued by the Professional Regulation Commission. (Guidelines on Self-Directed Learning Creditable Activities).",
  },
  {
    question: "Whom should I contact for inquiries?",
    answer:
      "The Conference Secretariat will respond to your queries and additional information requests through ricesecretariat@gmail.com.",
  },
];
